Mitchell George

mitchgeorge8@gmail.com | Columbus, OH | www.linkedin.com/in/mitchell-g-george

SUMMARY

Design Engineer with a B.S. in Electrical Engineering, full stack web development certification, and 5+ years of experience working with a team. Looking to apply analytical skills and close attention to detail in a fulltime Developer role.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Design Development Engineer

NIFCO AMERICA

Current

Ensure that every part meets the design intent, both aesthetically and functionally. Create part drawings, lead design changes, and improve part quality.

Customer Quality Engineer

NIFCO AMFRICA

2021-2022

Handled part quality complaints from a wide range of customers. Worked with cross-functional teams to establish root causes and implement permanent corrective actions.

EDUCATION

Certification Full Stack Web Development The Ohio State University	2022
Bachelor of Science Electrical Engineering Mount Vernon Nazarene University	2021
Associate of Applied Science Industrial Technology North Central State College	2017

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Resident Assistant

2018-2021

MOUNT VERNON NAZARENE UNIVERSITY

Worked with a team to enforce campus policies, plan student events, and foster a healthy community. Oversaw a dorm/apartment of students, serving as their main point of contact for questions and concerns.

ACTIVITIES		SKILLS
Honors Program	2017-2020	JavaScript MERN Stack REST APIs
Small group leader	2018-2021	Progressive Web Applications Object-Oriented
Sustainability Club leader	2020-2021	Programming Model-View-Controller Object-
Student mentor	2019	Relational Mapping Tailwind CSS SQL GraphQL HTML CSS